<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Rui Zhou</title>
    <link>https://r-zh.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Rui Zhou</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://r-zh.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>M.A.Sc VS M.Eng</title>
      <link>https://r-zh.github.io/post/master_type/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 09:49:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://r-zh.github.io/post/master_type/</guid>
      <description> I would like to share my experience about my view of M.A.Sc and M.Eng in English, Chinese and French. The following are the videos on the Youtube.
English Version   汉语版本   Version de Français   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Write the Master Thesis?</title>
      <link>https://r-zh.github.io/post/thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 11:50:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://r-zh.github.io/post/thesis/</guid>
      <description> I shared my experience about how to write my master thesis in English, Chinese and French. Here is the Playlist of videos on the Youtube.
English Version   汉语版本   Version de Français   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcom back to the Page &gt;_&lt;</title>
      <link>https://r-zh.github.io/post/memorandum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 10:06:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://r-zh.github.io/post/memorandum/</guid>
      <description> When suddenly remember I have the blog:  Go to the blog folder and open the Shell: Hugo server Search for How to write Markdown Check Hugo Academic if need New Post, Project, Publication Run git pull After changing, build public folder Run  git clone https://github.com/r-zh/r-zh.github.io.git  After changing, Upload the new commit  2020&amp;rsquo;s Plan  Thesis Defence  soon  learning Python Django Rich personal website - Structure for every post Drive license Join one vulunteer activity French Language  200 words 30 expression Grammar  Exercise  Taichi 24 Savate Iaido   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing For Exams</title>
      <link>https://r-zh.github.io/post/preparing_exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 14:22:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://r-zh.github.io/post/preparing_exam/</guid>
      <description>During the Study About the coming lecture (within 24 hours)  Preview the materials before the lecture. Make copy of slides and add notes During the lecture. Organized notes in textbook as a resource. Here is &amp;ldquo;what I learn&amp;rdquo; after lecture.  Memorize Chunking: Put the complex bodies into smaller chunks. Ex.
how do you remember the phone number? 5141231357? or 514-123-4757?  Classifying, summarizing, categorizing, sequencing, grouping, using acronyms, mnemonics</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exercise in Different Culture</title>
      <link>https://r-zh.github.io/post/exercise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 08:42:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://r-zh.github.io/post/exercise/</guid>
      <description> Savate   八段锦 
  形意拳   Iaido   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consideration before Rental</title>
      <link>https://r-zh.github.io/post/rental/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 09:44:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://r-zh.github.io/post/rental/</guid>
      <description>Bad experience  Don&amp;rsquo;t trust the landload compeletely. Before getting the key and clean house, don&amp;rsquo;t pay anything.  Confirm which room, which floor.  Check the door, make sure it won&amp;rsquo;t be locked by itself. Make sure the time to moving the luggage, be clear at which day and hour.  If it changes, remind what was discussed before and ask why. Confirm 10 minutes early if it is not clear at time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIY Dishes</title>
      <link>https://r-zh.github.io/post/food/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 19:23:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://r-zh.github.io/post/food/</guid>
      <description>邻居家小孩都馋哭了系列 所谓在家靠父母，出门吃饭还是自己做便宜。外面的菜太贵了，忒贵了，老贵了，自己做点，吃的时候要记得看着《风味人间》！
京酱肉丝  准备好肉，甜面酱，豆瓣酱，葱，姜，老抽，淀粉 处理材料  水淀粉中淀粉要少，显得水有点浑就行 肉的精瘦部分切成丝，和水淀粉放在一块，肥的部分剁一剁，放在碗里备用 葱、姜切成丁  肥肉下锅，中火熬（很长一段时间）油， 然后放葱姜炒出香味 一定要开大火，将肉和水淀粉放在锅里翻炒 待至七成熟，放入2勺甜面酱，1勺豆瓣酱，加一点点老抽染色，翻炒至尝一口觉得还行，就可以盛出来了        青椒肉丝  准备好肉，葱，姜，菜椒，老抽，淀粉 处理材料  水淀粉中淀粉要少，显得水有点浑就行 肉的精瘦部分切成丝，和水淀粉放在一块，肥的部分剁一剁，放在碗里备用 葱切成丁，菜椒切成丝  肥肉下锅，中火熬（很长一段时间）油， 然后放葱姜炒出香味 一定要开大火，将肉和水淀粉放在锅里翻炒 待至七成熟，加一点点老抽染色，放入菜椒丝，翻炒至尝一口觉得还行，就可以盛出来了 如果有隔天剩的米饭，而且还想吃个炒鸡蛋的话，就勇敢地去做吧，好吃的菜百搭        家庭专用火锅 准备材料：香菇 泡面 白菜 羊肉 酒

吃完肉后，喝一杯浓茶帮助消化，人生极大乐事</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>French Learning Tips</title>
      <link>https://r-zh.github.io/post/french/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 19:21:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://r-zh.github.io/post/french/</guid>
      <description>Standards:  Just focus on the words what we use most in chatting: Compared with our own language, habit, culture, self-introduce Be postive to talk with native speakers: Language is used to let other undersand us  200 words Conjonction    Words Meaning Words Meaning Words Meaning Words Meaning     et and ou or autre other d&amp;rsquo;abord first   aussi also mais but peut-être maybe ensuite then, hence   pour for toutefois however si if donc therefore   moi aussi me too pas moi not me même same alors so, then   depuis since dans in sur on à at   quoi de plus what&amp;rsquo;s more bien que although par by par per   assez enough plutôt rather trés very ne pas not    Verbe    Words Meaning Example  Words Meaning Example     être to be Êtes-vous marié?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git Commands in Usage</title>
      <link>https://r-zh.github.io/post/git/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 19:20:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://r-zh.github.io/post/git/</guid>
      <description>Overview Update website Using Hugo to set personal website has some issues about Git to attention. Source code and website code are independent.
   Category Source code Website Code     Creation Manually Automatically   File type .md .html   Usage Edit the Content Display the Information   Folder hugo root public    Therefore, we need to develop the source code firstly, and push it to git.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Development Summary</title>
      <link>https://r-zh.github.io/post/mobile/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 19:19:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://r-zh.github.io/post/mobile/</guid>
      <description>If you are urgent to create the App. Follow the link
 APICloud Gonative  They have the service for generate Mobile App automatically with H5 Webpages&amp;rsquo; link.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photoshop Tips</title>
      <link>https://r-zh.github.io/post/photoshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 16:46:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://r-zh.github.io/post/photoshop/</guid>
      <description> Create the dynamic picture  导入图片 File -&amp;gt; 设置图片大小（宽500px） 打开时间轴控件 逆向并设置时间 设置过度（每张1秒，间隔20张） 存储为网页可识别  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>